[{
        "Question": "Select a question to ask",
        "Answer": ""
    },{
        "Question": "What do you see?",
        "Answer": " A grid-1 location is below the red block. A grid-2 location is below the blue block. A grid-5 location is below the red block. A grid-6 location is below the blue block. A grid-9 location is below the red block. A red block is on the grid-1 location. A blue block is on the grid-2 location. A red block is on the grid-5 location. A blue block is on the grid-6 location. A red block is on the grid-9 location. I see a grid-3 location, a grid-4 location, a blue block, a grid-7 location and a grid-8 location."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is 'free'?",
        "Answer": "if a block is not on a location then it is free."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is 'clear'?",
        "Answer": "If an object is not below an object , then it is clear."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the red block-12?",
        "Answer": "A grid-1 location."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the red block-11?",
        "Answer": "A grid-9 location."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the red block-10?",
        "Answer": "A grid-5 location."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the blue block-15?",
        "Answer": "A grid-2 location."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the blue block-14?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the blue block-13?",
        "Answer": "A grid-6 location."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-1 location?",
        "Answer": "A red block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-2 location?",
        "Answer": "A blue block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-3 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-4 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-5 location?",
        "Answer": "A red block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-6 location?",
        "Answer": "A blue block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-7 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-8 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-9 location?",
        "Answer": "A red block."
    }
]


